The goal of this level is to train people to differentiate beats by BPM.
There are three groups of flowers here.
Each group beats at a particular rate.
When activated, the flower plays a loop at that rate once,
and its orb blinks at that BPM.
If another flower is activated during that playback,
it plays after the current one, and both play together.
If the BPMs match,
another flower can be added to the group during that time; otherwise,
the player starts over.
Game audio didn't get recorded in the Mac OS screen recording,
so leaving that to your imagination.
Once the entire group is activated, the selection orbs turn green,
and those flowers are no longer interactive.
The level doesn't tell the player what the goal is,
leaving them to figure out that what allows them to proceed is matching BPMs.
Further levels can be added based on harmony,
and adding the challenge of optimizing the order in which the group is activated,
if there's not enough time to physically get to all flowers in the group in arbitrary order because of space geometry.
The player can brute-force the level by testing all flowers against a single one and seeing which play together well.
However, the loop plays twice each time, forcing them to wait longer.
If they listen to each flower once and figure out which ones match just by listening,
they can collect the groups without time penalty.
The time penalty, fail count limit, point scoring,
and so on can be trivially added to encourage listening instead of brute-forcing.
The level geometry is a Gaussian Splat,
obtained from a world model generated with World Labs AI Marble,
from a picture generated by Gemini,
inspired by Buckminster Fuller's Dymaxion house architecture,
and automatically segmented with Nigel Hartman's Splat Analyzer.
The audio loops, as well as this voiceover, were generated by Claude.
The source code was one hundred percent vibe-coded with Claude,
based on the SensAI WebXR World Model template, built on Meta's IWER,
during the SensAI Hack hackathon by XR Bootcamp, slash, SensAI Hackademy.
The only thing made by a human in this project were prompts to various A Is: Gemini,
World Labs, and Claude.